hey guys I'm Tara and welcome to the
大家好，我是Tara，欢迎收看学习扎实的第一集
very first episode of learning solidity
by example in this video I'm gonna show
通过该视频中的示例，我将向您展示如何编写基本的智能合约
you how to write a basic smart contract
in solidity I'll show you how to write
我将向您展示如何编写您的第一个智能合约
your first smart contract compile it
deploy to above change simulator and
部署到上述变更模拟器，最后运行合约或在您的内部
finally run the contract or inside your
browser links to the code are in the
浏览器到代码的链接在下面的描述中，因此请先进行混音
description below so first go to remix
浏览器到代码的链接在下面的描述中，因此请去remix
Eternia morg this is our online code
remix这是我们的在线代码编辑器和我们的区块链模拟器
editor and our blockchain simulator once
the page loads click on the solidity
该页面加载后，单击“ solidity”按钮以创建您的第一个合约
button to create your first contract go
to the file explorer and click this plus
到文件浏览器，然后单击此加号按钮并创建一个新文件，我们将其命名为
button and create a new file we'll name
our smart contract hello world
我们的智能合约，您要做的第一件事
the very first thing that you want to do
in your contract is to specify the
您合约中的内容是在此处指定编译器版本
compiler version at the moment there
seems to be a bug in remix where the
似乎是混音中的错误，其中版本零的编译器指向第五点
compiler with version zero point five
point one and zero point five point two
第一点和零点五点第二点不起作用，因此我们将指定
do not work so we'll specify our
contract version 2 the greater than or
合约版本2大于或等于零分五分三
equal to zero point five point three and
that stands your politics we start with
这代表了您的政治，我们从关键字合约开始，我们将其命名为
a keyword contract and we'll name it
hello world this is actually a valid
你好世界，这实际上是有效的合约，但它什么也没做，所以
contract but it does nothing at all so
let's make it a little more interesting
让我们通过存储问候语使它更加有趣
by storing the greeting message we
create a string variable that's named
创建一个名为的字符串变量，该变量与我们的消息问候世界在
agree with our message hello world at
the moment this variable is only
当此变量只能在此合约内访问时，我们可以
accessible inside this contract we can
make it accessible outside the contract
通过将关键字“ public”（公共）设置为可在合约外部访问
by putting the keyword public I'll
explain more about the keyword public in
在其他视频中详细说明有关“公共”关键字的内容，我们的合约是
another video and our contract is
completed so now let's compile it take
完成后，现在让我们编译一下该编译图标
this solidity icon
the compiler is within our range greater
编译器在我们的范围内，大于等于零点，五点
than equal to zero point five point
three and less than zero point six
3，且小于零点，六，如果您单击下一步，则单击此编译按钮
next click on this compile button if you
don't see any errors or warnings here
在这里看不到任何错误或警告，这意味着您很好
that means you're good to go
also you'll see a green check here next
另外，您还会在此处看到绿色的对勾，接下来，我们会将合约部署到
we'll deploy our contract onto a
blockchain simulator running inside your
区块链模拟器在您的浏览器中运行，因此请进行部署和运行
browser so go to deploy and run
transactions make sure that our smart
交易确保我们的智能合约hello world dot soul是
contract hello world dot soul is
selected in hit deploy
在热门部署中选择
you can see that our contract is
您可以看到我们的合约已经部署在这里，让我们检查一下是否可以
deployed here let's check that we can
get the greeting message click on the
收到问候消息，单击灰色按钮，您可以在此处看到我们
grey button and you can see here that we
get our message
得到我们的消息
recap we learned how to write our first
回顾一下，我们学习了如何编写第一个智能合约集的编译器版本
smart contract set the compiler version
using the keyword pragma and how to
使用关键字pragma以及如何创建可公开访问的变量
create a publicly accessible variable
using the keyword public
使用关键字public
for watching and see you in the next
观看并在下一个视频中与您见面
video